{
    "id": "8d4449fee3324a1c9219d85d4c4e455c",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Beware of that ……………………….. in sheep’s clothing.",
            "description": "A wolf in sheep’s clothing is a hypocrite.",
            "answers": [
                "fox",
                "wolf",
                "jackal"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "After her husband’s death, she is struggling to keep the ……………………………….. from the door.",
            "description": "To keep the wolf from the door is to avert starvation.",
            "answers": [
                "tiger",
                "owl",
                "wolf"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The violence came to a ……………………….. when the police fired at the rioters.",
            "description": "To come to a head is to reach a crisis.",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "head",
                "peak"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He might plead the cause of the poor, but he is unlikely to put his hand in his ..........................................",
            "description": "To put your hand in your pocket is to donate money to a charity.",
            "answers": [
                "bag",
                "pocket",
                "drawers"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You see she has two strings to her ……………………………. She is a writer. She also does modeling.",
            "description": "To have two strings to your bow is to have two sources of income.",
            "answers": [
                "bow",
                "sitar",
                "violin"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They have threatened war to the …………………………….. if their demands are not granted.",
            "description": "A war to the knife is a deadly struggle.",
            "answers": [
                "spear",
                "dragon",
                "knife"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He joined the company as a cashier but now he is at the top of the …………………………..",
            "description": "When you are at the top of the tree you are at the highest position in an organization.",
            "answers": [
                "house",
                "tree",
                "ship"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I sent him about his …………………………… because I could no longer stand his insolence.",
            "description": "To send somebody about their business is to dismiss them rudely.",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "job",
                "business"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He says that he has rubbed …………………………… with many celebrities.",
            "description": "To rub shoulders with somebody is to be in close contact with them.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "shoulders",
                "hands"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have told you time and again not to poke your …………………………… into my business.",
            "description": "To poke your nose is to meddle in another person’s affairs.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "nose",
                "tongue"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the ……………………………. man of his boss.",
            "description": "The right hand man is the person who supports you the most.",
            "answers": [
                "right hand",
                "left hand",
                "second hand"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "After the death of his parents, his uncle took him under his …………………………….",
            "description": "To take somebody under your wing is to offer them protection. ",
            "answers": [
                "shoulder",
                "wings",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}